Destiny. Fate. Dreams.
These unstoppable ideals are
held deep in the heart of man.
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth.
People tell me my head's in the clouds.
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreaming of you.
You are the treasure I found.
So bright, so bold, and so elusive.
It's hard to look away.
Even though it's blinding me.
There are no words to
describe how I feel inside.
I'm really, really stuck on you.
I have to follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem.
Then I won't stop till I
get there, you will see.
You're all I need to have
the strength to believe.
We live in wonderland.
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem.
I'm gonna share them
with you, a love so true.
You're all I want,
together we can move on.
We live how we want to.
There is no limit to us.
We have the power of love.
But we don't wanna live ordinary lives.
But we have a chance to live in paradise.
We live in wonderland.
Ah, the snow, too bad.
Snow in this climate? Sure, why not?
Already happened once You just
missed it because you were asleep
Hey, what about you?
Do you think it's going to snow?
I wouldn't rule anything out.
But the sea you were in the
first time it snowed was special.
The seven magnetic fields
that emit from Reverse
Mountain tend to make
things particularly chaotic.
But that doesn't mean you should relax
your guard while sailing these waters.
The odds of it being as wild as
your first journey may be small.
Still, these waters aren't normal and are
certain to hold surprises of their own.
Remember, never underestimate the sea.
Hey, guys!
Anyone care to sample my special drink?
Hey, you guys want to
get out the fishing gear?
Fishing?
Hell yeah, I'm in.
Sounds good to me.
I'll even make you one of
my custom fishing rods.
You'll love it.
Well, somebody's sure thirsty.
Have another.
Look at him go!
Yeah, give him another one!
They're acting like idiots!
Maybe this will help.
Just relax.
These boys may go through
their goofy phases,
but when things get
rough, they get to work.
Trust me, I should know.
Sorry, I don't know what's wrong with me.
I'm getting worked up over nothing.
This ship will put you at ease.
You'll cheer up in no time.
Attaboy!
Yeah, they're funny.
Hey, look, it's a dolphin,
pirate's best friend.
Whoa, beautiful!
It's huge!
Ha ha ha ha!
Let's go!
Move it!
Okay, going.
Got it.
Take that side. Gotcha.
She was right.
Okay, hurry. Let's move.
Get ready.
It's gonna be a big one.
Nami, which direction now?
Give me a second, I'll check.
Port side, fall!
Turning fall!
There's no mistake,
Cactus Island and this one here are
definitely pulling against each other.
Our next stop!
This is it, our second
island in the Grand Line?
Mr. Three?
Yes, my dear, hold on.
There's nothing quite like
the rich aroma of Earl Grey.
I'm bored.
On the one hand, you say you're bored.
On the other, you don't
like working, correct?
Mm-hmm.
Then why don't you cease your complaining?
And revel in the enjoyment of
this rare slice of freedom,
Some circumstances have
generously afforded you.
How grand to be able to
take a long vacation.
A privilege few officers
ever get to indulge.
One more thing.
I would appreciate your
mindful and immediate
discretion in not calling
me by my codename in public.
Otherwise, people will
discover that I am indeed Mr.
Three.
Sure.
Incidentally,
I couldn't help noticing
you've been perusing
that piece of paper over
the last several days.
Why does it grab you so?
It's an order from boss.
Why didn't you tell me sooner?
It says Mr.
Five has been taken down.
If someone had to be terminated, I wish it
would have been someone useless like Mr.
Two.
So what would benefit
you with a fat promotion?
It's not that necessarily.
Rather, the downfall of Mr.
Five is hardly exciting news at all.
The man excelled at
nothing but his own idiocy,
clinging to his Devil Fruit
power like a drowning rat.
You are correct that a modicum
of my indifference stems
from the fact that Five's
misfortune brings me no gain.
All we may learn is power means
nothing if not properly harnessed.
Superior criminals are those who execute
their crimes using superior intellect.
Nevertheless, whoever beat Mr.
Five should be made an example of,
If for no other reason than to
preserve the reputation of terror,
our organization is
painstakingly cultivated,
and indeed for criminality as a whole.
I can see why they call
this place Little Garden.
I can't.
What's little about it?
Yeah, this island looks
pretty harsh if you ask me.
Why the cute name?
Yeah, it looks like a jungle out there.
Maybe we'd be better
off skipping this one.
We have to be careful.
I can't help but remember the
warning Miss All Sunday gave us.
So what?
We might be attacked by
giant monsters? Who knows?
Listen, I'm sure we can make it to the next
island without going ashore on this one.
The only way to reset
the log is to go ashore.
Not to mention we're in dire need
of restocking our food supply.
We didn't get so much as a
sack of flour in the last town.
Guys, there's our ticket in.
Huh?
Think they'll have a
barbecue restaurant here?
We didn't travel all
this way for barbecue.
I thought the point of
this visit was to get food.
Food, as in supplies
we're going to cook later?
Jeez, what are you thinking?
I don't know.
Oofsop might be right about this one.
Just take a look at the
gargantuan plant life here.
I've never seen anything
like it, not even in books.
You're so adorable.
Thank you. That's not funny.
I was talking to Nami.
What was that screeching?
It's all right, love.
It's only a bird.
Perfectly harmless, just like this jungle.
Nothing to worry about.
What's wrong?
What the hell's the matter
with you, you damn bird?
Oh, it's big. Could be tasty.
Hear that?
Is that the kind of noise you
expect to hear in a normal jungle?
That sounded like a volcano erupting.
We're all going to die!
A tiger!
It's gigantic!
What?
Luffy, what just happened?
I know normal.
This is definitely not it.
Someone explain to me how a mammoth tiger
can just keel over covered in blood?
Long bows and food, be damned!
We're not stepping foot on
that island and that's final!
We can still reset the
readings on the ship.
We'll just sit tight until then.
Right!
When that's done, we'll
leave and never look back.
Great!
Yeah, great!
We'll all just stay here.
Sanji, go make lunch.
You want lunch?
Yep, and one more thing.
Make it a great big pirate lunch
with lots of meat and no veggies.
I'm going to need some more energy.
Energy for what?
What are you doing?
You're not leaving here.
You know.
Beast, do you want to come along?
It's you.
I can't stop him.
He's too enthusiastic.
Is he crazy?
Somewhere out there is a monster big
enough to grind a tiger into base.
Saji, I'm starving.
Right, be patient.
and I'll have it to you as soon as I can.
Say, Luffy, would it be all
right if I come along with you?
Sure, sounds great. No!
Phoebe, you can't be serious!
Yeah, I'd rather not sit here with
nothing to do but worry about my troubles.
This will keep me busy
till the logs reset.
Out of the question, seriously!
It's way too dangerous for you out there!
I'll be fine.
Besides, I'll have Karoo with me.
Hey, something's wrong.
Karoo doesn't look too good.
You might be in shock.
Vivi, if you go exploring,
you'll need to eat.
I'll pack you a lunch.
Thanks.
While you're at it, could
you fix something for Karoo?
Of course.
You just leave it to me.
Now you're all set and ready to go.
two pirate lunches for Luffy and
Vivi and a special drink for Karoo.
Thanks.
Well, see you guys later.
Don't worry, everything will be fine.
Vivi, what a girl.
She's so brave.
And just what would you expect from someone
who could infiltrate the enemy's ranks?
I'm bored. I'm gonna take a walk.
Take a walk?
Hey, Zoro.
Wait up.
You know we're kind of
short on food, right?
If you find any animals that
appear edible, bring them back.
Okay, it's easy.
I could see why you'd want to send me,
because I could bring back something
you couldn't catch yourself.
What the hell does that mean?
I won't let that remark go unchallenged.
You're saying you can capture
bigger game than I can,
like my hunting skills are inferior?
Yeah, that's right.
Challenge accepted.
Okay, winner brings back
the most pounds of meat.
What do you mean pounds?
Because I'll bring back tons.
Why don't you let your hunting
do your talking for you?
Good luck, cook.
I will never understand it.
Why do those two jerks
have to be so competitive?
Don't cry.
If it makes you feel better, I'm just
as stumped by their behavior as you.
We're sitting ducks.
Don't you think I already know that?
Why didn't I think of that before?
Where are you going?
Nami, what's wrong?
That's not it.
Not this one either. Gah!
Gah! Nami! Whoa! Hey!
What the heck are you
looking for anyway, huh?
Quiet!
I remember reading about it in a book.
Uh, reading about what?
Little garden.
Hey, what's the matter?
Over here, check it out.
It's a shellfish that looks like a squid.
Shell squidfish!
How strange.
It sort of assembles an amminoid.
Cool, huh?
I've got a feeling someone's
been following me for a while.
Couldn't be.
Can't you see I'm busy?
Paul Yee Koo!
I don't know what you're supposed to
be, but I'm guessing you're edible.
Let me see, which one was it? Maybe...
I think I read it recently,
but I don't remember.
The title's on the tip of my tongue.
That's weird.
What's a sea king doing on land?
A dinosaur!
Awesome!
No way! This is unreal!
Huh?
Somehow this island has been frozen in
time, stuck in the age of the dinosaurs!
Travel in the Grand Line is so difficult,
so no species ever migrated
between the islands,
and their unique
ecosystems were preserved!
Some of these islands have developed
extremely sophisticated cultures,
both biological and sociological,
while others remain in a sort
of evolutionary stagnation with
little to no progression for several
thousands or tens of thousands,
or...
In this case, it seems,
even millions of years.
I can only assume that
it's the random climates
within the Grand Line
that make this possible.
I mean, what other explanation is there?
We're standing on the island
that predates mankind!
Luffy!
Are you insane?
Usopp! Usopp! Huh? Nami? What now?
So, did you find your book yet?
Uh, huh?
This is bad.
This island...
Strange.
Why do I get the sense that Nami needs me?
To those who reside here
and call this island home,
it must seem as if they have stumbled
upon their very own private garden.
Thus, I have aptly named this wondrous,
terrifying place Little Garden.
Louis Arnot, Explorer.
Well, what is the answer?
Could you repeat that?
I didn't catch it.
Please, sir?
I asked if you had any alcohol.
I drank mine.
We have a little.
Oh, you do?
That's perfect.
Um, there's just one thing.
It's not the drinking kind.
It's for cooking and disinfecting.
But if that's acceptable,
you're welcome to it all.
A dinosaur!
I'm Broggy, the Elbaf's
strongest warrior, Invincible!
Now I have dinner, and the two
of you are invited as my guests!
Hehehehe!
Huh?
You okay?
Just pretend you're dead.
No matter what happens,
don't move a muscle.
That plain dad only fools bears.
It won't work.
Huh?
Huh.
Whoa!
What an amazing view!
This is the perfect spot for our lunch.
We aren't here to have a picnic, Luffy.
We need to keep moving. Huh?
Oh, they have active volcanoes here.
Not only that, look, there's a
mountain with huge holes in it.
It's dangerous up there.
Come down already.
Let me know! This is awful!
He's been eating the lawn!
Oh, it got dark.
Whoa!
Oh, so hot!
Huh?
What fun.
That was glorious.
Watching the likes of you
grapple with longnecks
is the most entertainment
I've had in quite a while.
You are my first visitor in a long time.
Wow, you are huge! Are you human?
Greatest warrior of all Elba!
I am Dory!
It's a...
a giant!
I've heard that they exist, but
I've never actually seen one before.
Well, hi, I'm Luffy!
And I'm a pirate!
A pirate?
Well, good for you, my friend!
Gah, gah,
gah,
gah, gah, gah,
gah, gah, gah, gah, gah,
gah, gah,
g
Go on, eat hearty, my friends.
It tastes delicious.
I think I've lost my appetite.
Don't be shy now. Dig in.
No, I don't want to eat.
Huh?
Dinosaur meat is sweet.
I promise you it's quite tasty.
Well, I guess he's attempting to
fatten us up before he kills us.
We'll be plump and juicy.
I never thought he'd end like this.
He's a typical barbaric giant.
We're too young to die. Too young.
Maybe that's the appeal.
Well, wait.
It's too bad.
You don't know what a
scrumptious meal you're missing.
We can't eat until the log resets.
If we can keep our hunger and
waistlines in check, we might survive.
Yeah, but I don't know how much
longer I can hold out, Nami.
If I don't eat something pretty soon,
I'm not sure I'll have the strength
or willpower to resist his offer.
Loggy, sir?
Do you mind if I ask you a question?
What's on your mind, young lady?
Um, how long will it take to
reset the log on this island?
One full year.
A year?
If we waited that long to eat, we
wouldn't have stomachs to feed.
It's over.
We have to admit defeat.
Don't tell me you're
gonna fall asleep again.
You sure know how to cook, Giant.
Why, thanks for the compliment.
Your pirate goodies are
excellent too, my little friend.
although the portions are a little small.
Yeah, I know what you mean.
But the chef on my ship made it especially
for this trip, so I'm glad you liked it?
because otherwise I'd have to beat you up.
Was that a threat, shorty? Ah!
I like you, little pirate.
You're really funny.
Hey!
They're becoming fast friends.
I don't mean to pry, but why do you
choose to live out here all by yourself?
Don't you have a village to call home?
I came from a village, a place
of many warriors, called Elbath.
It once was home, but I
no longer call it that.
Why?
There are certain rules in
Elbath which must be obeyed.
Hmm, what kind of rules?
For example, if a fight breaks
out and neither side yields,
judgment is handed down by Elbath's god.
Whoever he deems to be
righteous will be declared
the winner and granted
survival as well as divine
protection so Elbeth's
God decides that doesn't
seem fair fair or not all
that matters is this is
our battleground as on
Elbeth our God will decide
who was righteous and
worthy of winning both the
duel and his life yeah yeah
yeah yeah we fought for
a century but Elbeth has
yet to choose a Champion,
You guys have been fighting
for more than a hundred years?
From a human's point of view, 100
years may seem like a long time,
but it isn't considering a giant's
average lifespan is three times yours.
Even with all the time in the world,
I think your desire would wane after
a hundred years of the same battle.
At this point, is there any
real animosity left between you?
Or are you just fighting to fight?
Wow, that's some explosion.
Well then, it's time to get going.
What was that? An eruption.
Huh?
I don't like that look.
He seems angry.
Please forgive me, but there
is something I must attend to.
What? You're leaving?
No choice.
That's the signal my opponent and I
used to mark the beginning of our fight.
A fight? With who? Where?
And more importantly, why?
Why?
I don't remember!
And before we realized,
it became our routine.
That volcano is our marker.
Whenever it erupts, we begin.
It's senseless.
How could you have so much hatred for
someone that you'd fight them for a century?
What could have happened
to make you this mad?
Vivi, that's enough.
That's not what this is about, okay?
You're right.
This is about honor.
I have forgotten!
The reason for our brawl!
The odds that you'll
find it are slim to none.
The world's such a big
place, the oceans are wide.
Tomocopo won't help you find it,
just give up, it's astronomical.
If you've been so!
If someone tries to
keep us from moving on!
The factor behind our
back just keeps us strong.
It's too bad cause we're still
selling for what's so fun for y 'all?
Just leave us alone.
It may be for this
chasing impossible things.
But I've just gotta try.
The crazier the dream The
more ambition I'm gonna need.
It may be for this driving home But
I know that I've just gotta fly.
We'll follow the sea The greater
paradise We're gonna fly.
Don't give up, just keep up crying.
And you say that you're closer to
The horizon of your dreams?